thecount.com 2015-06-17

# Privacy | Contact TheCount - TheCount.com

Anyone viewing TheCount.com does so at their own risk. The information included in or available through TheCount.com, sites/services may include inaccuracies or typographical errors.

This privacy policy may change from time to time. This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [TheCount.com](http://thecount.com/ "thecount.com killer gossip"). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

This site may contain links to other websites operated by third parties (“linked sites”). You acknowledge that TheCount.com and its sponsors neither endorse nor are affiliated with the linked site and are not responsible for any content of any linked site or any link contained in a link site, or any changes or updates to such sites. You also acknowledge that TheCount.com is providing these links to you only as a convenience.

You specifically agree that TheCount.com is not responsible or liable for any threatening, defamatory, obscene, offensive or illegal content or conduct of any other party or any infringement of another’s rights, including intellectual property rights. You specifically agree that TheCount.com is not responsible for any content sent using and/or included in a sites/service by any third party.

In no event shall TheCount.com be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special, consequential damages or any damages whatsoever including, without limitation, damages for loss of use, data or profits, arising out of or in any way connected with the use or performance of the TheCount.com sites/services, with the delay or inability to use the TheCount.com sites/services or related services, the provision of or failure to provide services, or for any information, software, products, services and graphics obtained through the TheCount.com sites/services, or otherwise arising out of the use of the TheCount.com sites/services, whether based on contract, tort, negligence, strict liability or otherwise. TheCount.com does not endorse in anyway any advertisers/ contents of advertisers on its webpages. please therefore verify the veracity of all information on your own before undertaking reliance and actioning thereupon. TheCount.com shall not be responsible nor liable for any consequential damages arising on account of your relying on the contents of the advertisement.

Images appearing on this website are assumed to be taken from public domain and or credited appropriately, unless otherwise specified. The copyright (if any) of an image belongs to their original publisher / photographer / copyright holder as the case may be. If you feel an image appearing on this website is not appropriately credited or appears in error, please [contact us](http://thecount.com/contact "http://thecount.com/contact").

Any links provided or advertisements displayed on our site are for informational purposes only and we are not responsible for any damages or consequences. However, if you find any unsuitable link / advertisement, then please contact us above giving detail of such material.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

   • See what data we have about you, if any.

   • Change/correct any data we have about you.

   • Have us delete any data we have about you.

   • Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**Cookies**  
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

**If other organizations use cookies or other devices that track site visitors to your site, insert a paragraph like this in your privacy policy:**

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Sharing**  
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

Partners: We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
